- Brent Spiner?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)I don't care.
(Leonard:)Really? Brent Spiner,
Mr. Data himseIf. You love him.
(Sheldon:)I did, but I think
I've kind of outgrown Star Trek.
(Sheldon:)You know, stock characters,
Iudicrous plots, beam me up.
(Sheldon:)What a load of hooey.
(Howard:)I'm going.
Live long and prosper, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, even that. You look like a dork.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Howard, Bernadette's here!
(Howard:)Tell her I'm not home!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)What kind of a schmuck
play is that? She can hear you shouting!
- Can we talk?
- You can. I have nothing to say.
(Wil:)All right.
(Bernadette:)I just wanted to tell you I'm sorry
I said something to your mother.
(Howard:)I was gonna tell her eventually
but you went behind my back.